it's the dawn of a new day and I'm saying this out loud to keep myself committed to it but
you know I spend a lot of time on here going back and forth with people who actually have
no interest in learning with people who have nothing additive to bring to the conversation
and with people who just simply have very different values in my own
and you get tricked into thinking that you owe those people space that you owe them people
time and that you as an educator are expected to convince them however we all know that there are
many different educators and I understand that that's just not my job that's not my role that's
not my purpose my purpose is to teach those who want to be taught to interact with those who want
to teach each other and this internet makes it very difficult for people to do that in a very
altruistic and genuine way they find themselves literally insulted when you respond back to them
with the same energy that they have brought to you one of disingenuousness one of passive aggression
etc and none of that is the type of energy and vibration that is helpful to fighting the actual
evils that we are facing so if you want to remain on this page think before you speak if your goal is
to just get some off fine I mean you'll do so and you'll be blocked and it won't have mattered
but as of today I have decided that I really have to interact with this space much more responsibly
oh those are my hard-boiled eggs
I need to interact with this space much more responsibly not just for myself but for those
who actually want to be here and if you want an even more responsibly interactive with space
come and join us over at the SEAL Squad on Patreon it's five dollars a month and you get a community
beyond me anywho wanted to share that with you and also share with myself so I can stand on it
support a real one